Guide to the International Nepal Fellowship Records
Yale University Divinity School Library
International Nepal Fellowship records
1932-2014
RG 214
Yale University Divinity School Library
25
61 boxes
These are the official archives of the International Nepal Fellowship, formerly known as the Nepal Evangelistic Band. The International Nepal Fellowship is a Christian international non-government organization working in Nepal. It helps people affected by tuberculosis, leprosy, disability, HIV / AIDS and drug abuse, facilitates development among poor communities, runs medical camps and provides medical training.
International Nepal Fellowship
Immediate Source of Acquisition
Gift of the International Nepal Fellowship, Worldwide, 2009
Custodial History
These archives were previously housed at the University of Edinburgh.
Conditions Governing Access
The materials are open for research.
Biographical / Historical
International Nepal Fellowship, Worldwide is an international non-government organization, registered in Australia as a non-profit company limited by guarantee. INF Worldwide has its official registered head office in Australia, however its International Service Office is in Nepal's capital Kathmandu and it works in Nepal through five-yearly agreements with the Nepali government's Social Welfare Council. INF Worldwide finds, trains and supports expatriate volunteers to work with INF Nepal and other partner organisations, including Nepali government health and training institutions and community-based organisations. INF has six offices across the globe, two in Nepal, and one in New Zealand, Australia, North America and the UK.
The INF's district-based, integrated programmes include hospital and rehabilitation services for people with disabilities, health and development programmes with marginalized communities, medical camps, assistance for organizations working for people with disabilities, HIV / AIDS education, testing, counseling and care, work among displaced people, TB and leprosy clinics. INF sends personnel into government institutions and other organizations to provide health services training.
INF was born in 1936 when its founding missionary Dr Lily O'Hanlon felt called to Nepal. Dr. O'Hanlon and Hilda Steele traveled to India where they worked with Indians and Nepali's on the border of Nepal until they were able to register as the 'Nepal Evangelistic Band' in Lucknow on the 22nd February 1943. By 1940 the Band was a team of ten expatriates and nineteen Nepali volunteers. Along with Dr. Ruth Watson, known as "Kanchhi Doctor", three nursing sisters and team of Nepali colleagues, they trekked to Pokhara in November 1952, establishing a general hospital, the Shining Hospital, in April 1953. In 1957 the mission opened Green Pastures Hospital for leprosy patients. In the 1960s the mission expanded its work into remoter areas opening village clinics in Baglung, Sikha and Beni. From the 1970s the government of Nepal's 5th 5-year plan included significant health proposals, and INF began developing working relationships and co-operative projects with the government, including the building, equipping and staffing of Gandaki Zonal Hospital, which later became the Western Regional Hospital, the main hospital in Pokhara. The mission also signed an agreement with the government for a major leprosy control project in West and Mid-West Nepal, and was working in the areas of Tuberculosis control and community health. In the 1990s the mission began working in the areas of drug and alcohol abuse and AIDS prevention. The mission has also been involved in education and training programmes for staff employed by the government and NGOs, and for its own staff and their children.
Scope and Contents
These archives provide valuable documentation of the founding of the Nepal Evangelistic Band / International Nepal Fellowship, and the operations of the organization in Nepal from the 1950s primarily through the 1990s. The collection forms part of the Himalayan collection at Yale Divinity School, which also include the archives of the United Mission to Nepal, Central Asia Fellowship, and the Nepal Church History Project.
The INF archives were organized and described by Betty Young while housed at the Centre for the Study of World Christianity, University of Edinburgh. The organization and classification system devised by Ms. Young have been kept intact.
The papers in Series I, Field Business, consist of constitutions and policies of the Nepal Evangelistic Band / International Nepal Fellowship, agreements with the His Majesty's Government of Nepal (HMG Nepal), annual reports, annual general meetings and conferences, minutes of the Field Council and other field committees, finance, correspondence, staffing, education and training, study on the impact of International Nepal Fellowship programmes in Nepal.
Series II, Projects, Programmes and Areas of Work, contains minutes, correspondence, project proposals, statistics, reports, surveys and evaluations related to INF"s work. This series also includes a section of historical documentation, including the diaries of founder Lily O'Hanlon.
The records in Series III, Home Ends, consist of minutes and correspondence of the UK, Australian, and New Zealand Home Councils, of INF (USA), the INF Netherlands Committee, and from the Philippines and Singapore. Series III also includes periodicals of the home offices such as Himalayan Helpers and Summit, and other material related to youth work in UK.
The collection of Newsletters / Prayer Letters in Series IV consists of newsletters and prayer letters from individual missionaries, Prayer Brief, INF Praying, Baglung Bulletin, Burtibang Newsletter, Gorahi Mail, News from Surkhet, Friends of WRH Newsletter, and Itram Inkings.
Series V, Publications, consists of: periodical publications including Lengthen & Strengthen, Prayer Notes, Nepal Evangelistic Band Newsletter, Today in Nepal and Nepal Evangelistic Band Australian Newsletter; leaflets about INF and life in Nepal; calendars; articles, pamphlets and books written by INF missionaries.
The Audio-Visual Material of Series VI includes interviews, talks, memorial services (including services for Dr. Ruth Watson and Dr. Lily O'Hanlon), conference sessions and slide commentaries on audio cassettes; scripts for videos and for slide presentations; one video (of the funeral service for Linda Sims).
Photographs, Series VII, include loose photographs of the early work of the Nepal Evangelistic Band; photographs of individuals and groups of missionaries and Nepali Christians; photographs of work in the Pokhara area, including Gandaki Boarding School; Himalayan Helpers Summer Camp, 1979; International Nepal Fellowship HQ Conference, 1996, two albums compiled by Hilda Steele; Nepal Evangelistic Band albums, and an album of photographs of King Birendra's visit to Gandaki Zonal Hospital, 1985.
The 2014 Addendum, Series X, brings publications and reports of the INF up to date.
Arrangement
I. Field Business (A), 1936-1998
II. Projects, Programmes, Areas of Work (B), 1932-1998
III. Home Ends (C), 1955-1999
IV. Newsletters / Prayer Letters (D), 1950-2005
V. Publications (E), 1954-2001
VI. Audio-Visual Material (F), 1978-2000
VII. Photographs (G), 1954-1996
VIII. Maps and Posters (H)
IX. Confidential Files (I), 1954-1997
X. Addendum - 2014
Missions -- Nepal; Missions -- China -- Tibet Autonomous Region; International Nepal Fellowship; Nepal Evangelistic Band
- Field Business (A), 1936-1998; Series I
  - Constitution, Planning, Policies Mission-Wide Concerns: A/01
    - Constitution and Related Matters: A/01/01, 1936-1971
      - Constitution, Rules Regulations, Principles Practice, Memorandum of Association (Nepal Evangelistic Band): A/01/01/01, 1936 - 1941 (Box 1, Folder 1)
      - Declaration of Trust of the Nepal Evangelistic Band: A./01/01/02, 1963 (Box 1, Folder 2)
      - Constitution and Principles Practice of the International Nepal Fellowship: A/01/01/03, 1971-1997 (Box 1, Folder 3)
    - Policies: A/01/02, 1974-1997
      - Miscellaneous policies, includiing categories of workers within INF, scholarship polilcy, outstations: history and purpose; housing policy for Pokhara, contingency plans in event of civil disturbance: A/01/02/01, 1982-1990 (Box 1, Folder 4)
      - Applications policy for candidates to INF, including forms, procedures, recruitment and selection policies: A/01/02/02, 1975-1988 (Box 1, Folder 5)
      - Assessment policy, including forms, interviews: A/01/02/03, 1978-1988 (Box 1, Folder 6)
      - Furlough and home leave policy, including forms, procedures, questionnaire, expenses: A/01/20/04, 1976-1989 (Box 1, Folder 7)
      - Optional two-year policy; comments re. lengths of term and furlough: A/01/02/05, 1983-1985 (Box 2, Folder 1)
      - Divorce policy: A/01/02/06, 1982-1995 (Box 2, Folder 2)
      - Acupuncture: A/01/02/07, 1997 (Box 2, Folder 3)
      - Pastoral Care Policy, including reports of Pastoral Care consultations, report on responses to questionnaire "Experiences of living in INF centres": A/01/02/08, 1990-1991 (Box 2, Folder 4)
    - Planning and structures: A/01/03, 1983-1998
      - Seven-year plan: A/01/03/01, 1983-1989 (Box 2, Folder 5)
      - Long term plans / future plans, including speech of John Bradley, discussion notes, survey, re. Nepalization of INF: A/01/03/02, 1990-1998 (Box 2, Folder 6)
      - Management structure, including job descriptions: A/01/03/03, 1984-1993 (Box 2, Folder 7)
    - Mission-wide concerns: A/01/04, 1979-1995
      - Open Forums, including re. questions of finance, Field Council, secondary education for missionaries' children in Nepal, accepatnace of cnadidates who have been divorce, assessment, etc.: A/01/04/01, 1984-1989 (Box 2, Folder 8)
      - Spiritual life, including re. prayer, charismatic mataters, worship, spiritual warfare: A/01/04/02, 1979-1995 (Box 2, Folder 9)
      - Wholistic mission, including paper on wearing tikas, commitment of INF: A/01/04/03, 1990-1991 (Box 2, Folder 10)
  - Agreements with Nepal Government: A/02, 1952-1995
    Scope and Contents
    Agreements with His Majesty's Government of Nepal
    - Letters of permission and agreements:: A/02/01, 1952-1980
      For individual projects
      - Early permission letters to Lily O'Hanlon, including re. Pokhara hospital, registration of doctors: A/02/01/01, 1952-1960 (Box 3, Folder 1)
      - Agreements for individual projects, including re. Pokhara leprosy hospital: A/02/01/02, 1973-1976 (Box 3, Folder 2)
    - Original signed agreements: A/02/02, 1976-1986
      - Original signed agreements for individual projects, including Leprosy Control Project, letter of exchange to Institute of Medicine, Tribhuvan University: A/02/02/01, 1976-1986 (Box 3, Folder 3)
      - Original signed copies of general agreements: A/02/02/02, 1985 (Box 3, Folder 4)
    - General agreements and project agreements: A/02/03, 1980-2000
      - General agreements and project agreements, including re. Leprosy Control Project, Social Services national Coordination Council, Save the Children Fund, merger of Shining Hospital and Gandaki Zonal Hospital, operation of Lalitpur District Health Services, Nepal Eye Hospital: A/02/03/01, 1980-1985 (Box 3, Folder 5)
      - General agreements and project agreements, including renewals, Leprosy Control Program, clinic and community health project in Tibetan campls, Gandaki Zonal Hospital, Pokhara, discussions with Nepali government officials: A/02/03/02, 1985-1990 (Box 3, Folder 6)
      - Agreements on mutual co-operation between His Majesty's Government (HMG) Nepal and INF; including letters of exchange re. Institute of Medicine, Tuberculosis Programme, Community Health Programme, Western Regional Hospital (Pokhara), Leprosy Mission (International): A/02/03/02, 1985-1990 (Box 3, Folder 7)
      - General agreement and project agreements, including re. Public Health Service, Curative Services and training, Deutsches Ausstzigen-Hilfswerk, Community Health Programme, Leporsy Control Project, funding for INF, goods imported, discussions with Nepali government officials: A/02/03/03, 1990-1995 (Box 3, Folder 8)
      - General agreement and project agreements, including re. projects noted above: A/02/03/04, 1995-2000 (Box 3, Folder 9)
  - Reports: A/03, 1959-1997
    - Annual reports: A/03/01, 1959-1997
      - Nepal Evangelistic Band: A/03/01/01, 1959-1970 (Box 4, Folder 1)
      - International Nepal Fellowship: A/03/01/02, 1971-1984 (Box 4, Folder 2)
      - International Nepal Fellowship: A/03/01/03, 1987-1997 (Box 4, Folder 3)
      - Reports to HMG Nepal: A/03/01/04, 1986-1990 (Box 4, Folder 4)
    - Director's reports: A/03/02, 1992-1996
      - Reports to INF International Council: A/03/02/01, 1992-1993 (Box 4, Folder 5)
      - Quarterly reports to Home Ends: A/03/02/02, 1992-1997 (Box 4, Folder 6)
  - Meetings: A/04, 1964-1997
    - Annual General Meetings and Bi-annual meetings: A/04/01, 1964-1994
      - Nepal Evangelistic Band: A/04/01/01, 1964-1972 (Box 4, Folder 7)
      - International Nepal Fellowship: A/04/01/02, 1973-1979 (Box 4, Folder 8)
      - International Nepal Fellowship: A/04/01/03, 1980-1985 (Box 5, Folder 1)
      - International Nepal Fellowship: a/04/01/0/4, 1987-1994 (Box 5, Folder 2)
    - Conferences and international conferences: A/04/02, 1980-1992
      - INF conferences, including International Field Conference, Surkhet conference: A/04/02/01, 1980-1986 (Box 5, Folder 3)
      - International Conference: A/04/02/02, 1987 (Box 5, Folder 4)
      - International Conference business meetings: A/04/02/02, 1987 (Box 5, Folder 5)
      - INF conferences, including Pokhara and Surkhet conferences: A/04/02/03, 1987-1992 (Box 5, Folder 6)
      - International Conference: A/04/02/04, 1993 (Box 5, Folder 7)
      - INF conferences: A/04/02/05, 1994- (Box 5, Folder 8)
  - Minutes of Field Council Committees: A/05, 1958-1996
    - Field Council: A/05/01, 1958-1996
      - Minute books, vols. 1-2: A/05/01/01, 1958-1963 (Box 8, Folder 4-5)
      - Minute book, vol. 3: A/05/01/01, 1963-1966 (Box 6, Folder 1)
      - Minute book, vol. 4: A/05/01/01, 1966-1969 (Box 8, Folder 6)
      - Minute books, vols. 5-7: A/05/01/01, 1970-1982 (Box 6, Folder 2-4)
      - Minute books, vols. 8-9: A/05/01/01, 1983-1987 (Box 7, Folder 1-2)
      - Unbound minutes: A/05/01/02, 1959-1965 (Box 7, Folder 3)
      - Unbound minutes: A/05/01/03-A/05/01/05, 1966-1980 (Box 8, Folder 1-3)
      - Unbound minutes: A/05/01/06- A.05/01/08, 1981-1994 (Box 9, Folder 1-4)
    - Field Council Admin and Finance Committee: A/05/02, 1985-1993
      - Unbound minutes: A/05/02/01, 1985-1989 (Box 9, Folder 5)
      - Unbound minutes:A/05/02/02, 1990-1993 (Box 10, Folder 1)
      - Minute books: A/05/02/03, 1987-1993 (Box 10, Folder 2-3)
    - Personnel Committee and subcommittees: A/05/03, 1985-1995
      - Personnel Committee:A/05/03/01, 1984-1994 (Box 10, Folder 4-5)
      - Candidates Section of Personnel Committee / Candidates Committee: A/05/03/02, 1985-1992 (Box 11, Folder 1)
      - Candidates and Postings Committee:A/05/03/03, 1994 (Box 11, Folder 2)
    - Medical Co-ordinating Committee: A/05/04, 1986-1993
      - Medical Co-ordinating Committee: A/05/04/01-A/05/04/02, 1986-1993 (Box 11, Folder 3-4)
    - Other field committees: A/05/05, 1980-1996
      - Publications Co-ordinating Committee: A/05/05/01, 1986-1989 (Box 11, Folder 5)
      - Publicity Co-ordinating Committee: A/05/05/02, 1990-1996 (Box 11, Folder 6)
      - HQ Management Committee: A/05/05/03, 1988-1991 (Box 11, Folder 7)
      - Management Board and subcommittees: A/05/05/04, 1993-1994 (Box 11, Folder 8)
      - Employment Policy Committee: A/05/05/05, 1987-1993 (Box 11, Folder 9)
  - Field departments and business: A/06, 1963-1998
    - Publicity Department: A/06/01
      - Miscellaneous documents relating to Publicity Department: A/06/01/01, 1986-1997 (Box 11, Folder 10)
    - Finance Department: A/06/02
      - Budget estimates and financial reports: A/06/02/01, 1963-1986 (Box 11, Folder 11)
      - Invoices and receipts, ledger entries, financial records: a/06/02/03, 1964-1998 (Box 11, Folder 12)
    - INF and the Church: A/06/3
      - Documents relating to INF and the Church in general: A/06/03/01, 1974-1998 (Box 12, Folder 1)
      - Leaders' Seminars: A/06/3/02, 1989-1995 (Box 12, Folder 2)
      - Nepali Church Support Ministries / Keith Cope Project: A/06/03/03, 1990-1992 (Box 12, Folder 3)
  - Field Correspondence: A/07, 1969-1997
    - General field correspondence: A/07/01/01, 1972-1997 (Box 12, Folder 4)
    - Correspondence with Outstations: Surkhet: A/07/02/01, 1977-1988 (Box 12, Folder 5-6)
    - Correspondence with Outstations: Ghorahi: A/07/02/02, 1974-1983 (Box 12, Folder 7-8)
    - Correspondence with Outstations: Beni / Baglung / Sikha: A/07/02/03, 1959-1973 (Box 12, Folder 9)
    - Correspondence with Outstations: Beni / Baglung / Sikha: A/07/02/03, 1973-1978 (Box 13, Folder 1)
    - Correspondence with Outstations: Nautanwa / Bharahawa: A/07/02/04, 1970-1973 (Box 13, Folder 2)
    - Kathmandu Centre: A/07/03/01, 1986-1989 (Box 13, Folder 3)
    - Correspondence re Visas (including C. Root): A/07/04/01 (Box 13, Folder 4)
    - Correspondence and Papers re 40th Anniversary: A/07/05/01, 1991-1992 (Box 13, Folder 5)
    - Correspondence with Cindy Perry: A/07/06/01, 1991-1996 (Box 13, Folder 6)
    - Field Correspondence with UK Home Council – General: A/07/07/01, 1969-1991 (Box 13, Folder 7-11)
    - Personnel Secretary/Department with UK Home Secretary: A/07/07/02, 1985-1986 (Box 14, Folder 1-2)
    - Treasurer with UK Home Secretary: A/07/07/03, 1984-1986 (Box 14, Folder 3)
    - Administrator with UK Home Secretary: A/07/07/04, 1984-1987 (Box 14, Folder 4-5)
    - Field Correspondence with CIGM/ICF: A/07/08/01, 1965-1990 (Box 14, Folder 6)
    - Field Correspondence with CBM (Christoffel Blindenmission): A/07/08/02, 1976-1990 (Box 14, Folder 7)
    - Field Correspondence with DMG (Deutsche Missions Gemeinschaft): A/07/08/03, 1971-1989 (Box 14, Folder 8)
    - Field Correspondence with Tea Fund (UK and Netherlands): A/07/08/04, 1977-1986 (Box 14, Folder 9)
    - Field Correspondence with United Mission to Nepal: A/07/08/05, 1973-1985 (Box 15, Folder 1)
    - Field Correspondence with Leibenzeller Mission: A/07/08/06, 1981-1982 (Box 15, Folder 2)
    - Field Correspondence with Wiedenest: A/07/08/07, 1966-1997 (Box 15, Folder 3-5)
    - Field Correspondence with WEC: A/07/08/08, 1961-1985 (Box 15, Folder 6)
    - Field Correspondence with World Concern: A/07/08/09, 1978-1990 (Box 15, Folder 7)
    - Field Correspondence with Miscellaneous Asian Based Missions: A/07/08/10, 1986-1998 (Box 16, Folder 1)
    - Field Correspondence with British Embassy: A/07/08/11, 1986-1990 (Box 16, Folder 2)
    - Field Correspondence with Embassy of the United States of America: A/07/08/12, 1979-1990 (Box 16, Folder 3)
  - Staffing: A/08
    - Staffing Needs: A/08/01/01, 1978-1995 (Box 16, Folder 4)
    - Staffing Reviews: A/08/02/01, 1983-1985 (Box 16, Folder 5)
    - Personnel Correspondence and Papers: A/08/03/01, 1981-1998 (Box 16, Folder 6)
  - Education and Training: A/09
    - Education and Training – General: A/09/01/01 (Box 16, Folder 7)
    - Language and Orientation Training (LOT): A/09/0/201, 1991-1998 (Box 16, Folder 8)
    - Kathmandu International Study Centre (KISC): A/09/03/01, 1985-1994 (Box 17, Folder 1-2)
    - Inservice Training (Shining Hospital Staff): A/09/04/01, 1983-1988 (Box 17, Folder 3)
    - PSC Pokhara: A/09/05/01, 1983-1987 (Box 17, Folder 4-5)
    - Mark Selwood Training Centre: A/09/06/01 (Box 17, Folder 6)
  - Impact Study for His Majesty's Government of Nepal: A/10, 1990
    - General Programs in Nepal: A/10/01/01, ca.1990 (Box 17, Folder 7)
    - Preliminary Study on Impact of International Nepal Fellowship (INF): A/10/01/02, ca.1990 (Box 17, Folder 8)
    - Secondary Data/Papers/Reports Supplies by INF for the Study: A/10/01/03, ca.1990 (Box 17, Folder 9)
    - Contents of Impact Study by IMF for HMG: A/10/01/03, ca.1990 (Box 17, Folder 10)
    - General Documents: A/10/01/03, ca.1990 (Box 17, Folder 11)
    - General Agreement and Letter of Exchange 5th Dec. 1985-1990: A/10/01/03, ca.1990 (Box 17, Folder 12)
    - Leprosy Control Project: A/10/01/03, ca.1990 (Box 18, Folder 1-4)
    - Green Pastures (GP) Leprosy Hospital: A/10/01/03, ca.1990 (Box 18, Folder 5)
    - Secondary Data/Papers/Reports Supplied by INF for the Study: A/10/01/03, ca.1990 (Box 18, Folder 6)
    - Tuberculosis Program (TBP): A/10/01/03, ca.1990 (Box 18, Folder 7)
    - Surveys Baseline Studies Evaluation Reports Pokhara Reports Community Health: A/10/01/03, ca.1990 (Box 19, Folder 1)
    - BCHP Annual Reports, Other Studies: A/10/01/03, ca.1990 (Box 19, Folder 2)
    - Community Health Programme (CHP): A/10/01/03, ca.1990 (Box 19, Folder 3)
    - Shining and Bazaar Clinics in Pokhara: A/10/01/03, ca.1990 (Box 19, Folder 4)
    - Western Regional Hospital: A/10/01/03, ca.1990 (Box 19, Folder 5)
    - Institute of Medicine (IOM): A/10/01/03, ca.1990 (Box 19, Folder 6)
    - Laboratory Services Apt. (LSA) now joint with UMN: A/10/01/03, ca.1990 (Box 19, Folder 7)
    - Health Education Materials DPT (HMO) (Development Communication Productions: A/10/01/03, ca.1990 (Box 19, Folder 8)
    - GHOCAHI: A/10/01/03, ca.1990 (Box 19, Folder 9)
    - Baglung, Sikha and Beni, etc. (Dhaulagiri): A/10/01/03, ca.1990 (Box 19, Folder 10)
    - Surkhet: A/10/01/03, ca.1990 (Box 19, Folder 11)
    - Boy's Boarding School (with UMN):A/10/01/03, ca.1990 (Box 19, Folder 12)
- Projects, Programmes, Areas of Work (B), 1932-1998; Series II
  - Various projects/programmes: B/01 - B/12
    - Projects – General: B/01/01/01 (Box 20, Folder 1)
    - Gandak. Boarding School (GBS): B/02/01/01, 1966-1981 (Box 20, Folder 2)
    - Institute of Medicine (IOM): B/03/01/01, 1979-1985 (Box 20, Folder 3)
    - Laboratory Services Department (LSD): B/04/01/01, 1980-1986 (Box 20, Folder 4)
    - Health Education Materials Department (HEMO): B/05/01/01, 1983-1987 (Box 20, Folder 5)
    - Medical Supplies Department (MSD): B/06/01/01, 1986-1991 (Box 20, Folder 6)
    - Development Communications Project (DCP): B/07/01/01, 1987-1993 (Box 20, Folder 7)
    - TSP/TSO/TAP Technical Services Programme, Technical Services Department, Technical Assistance Program: B/08/01/01, 1986-1991 (Box 21, Folder 1)
    - Community Development Training Programme: B/09/01/01, 1992-1995 (Box 21, Folder 2)
    - The Far West: B/10/01/01, 1982-1993 (Box 21, Folder 3)
    - Nepalganj Centre: B/11/01/01, 1995-1998 (Box 21, Folder 4)
    - Drug/Alcohol Abuse and AIDS Prevention Programme: B/12/01/01, 1990- (Box 21, Folder 5)
  - Historical documents: B/13
    - Nepal Evangelistic Band – Early Work: B/13/01/01 (Box 21, Folder 6)
    - Lily O'Hanlon's Prayer Letters: B/13/02/01, 1932-1948 (Box 21, Folder 7)
    - O'Hanlon's Correspondence with Jonathan Lindell: B/13/02/02, 1942-1943 (Box 21, Folder 8)
    - O'Hanlon's Correspondence with Colin Molyneaux (HC Secretary UK): B/13/02/03, 1963-1970 (Box 21, Folder 9)
    - O'Hanlon's Correspondence with UK Home Council/Secretary: B/13/02/04, 1970-1982 (Box 22, Folder 1)
    - O'Hanlon's Diaries: B/13/03/01, 1933-1944, 1962 (Box 22, Folder 2-5)
  - Hospitals: B/14
    - Shining Hospital/Gandaki Zonal Hospital/Western Regional Hospital General: B/14/01/01, 1953-1990 (Box 22, Folder 6)
    - Shining Hospital/GZH/WRH – Correspondence re Agreement/Permission to Work: B/14/02/01, 1952-1962 (Box 23, Folder 1)
    - Shining Hospital/GZH/WRH Correspondence – General B140202 Shining Hospital/GZH/WRH Correspondence – General: B/14/02/01, 1966-1985 (Box 23, Folder 2-3)
    - Minutes Shining Hospital/Shining Community Health and TB Centre: B/14/03/02 (Box 23, Folder 4)
    - Minutes – GZH/WRH: B/14/03/03, 1984--1997 (Box 24, Folder 1-2)